Ellen Gubbels

425-923-8586

Efg20185337@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ellengubbels

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

I have twelve plus years of experience office administrative, recruiting, human resources, purchasing, customer service experience. I bring extensive experience as an office manager and administrative assistant duties in a fast-pace environment. Strong leadership, negotiating skills, excellent communication and collaboration, planning, and problem-solving skills. I am a self-starter, detail-oriented and strive to learn the needs of my internal and external customers. Exceptional computer skills including Microsoft and Google products as well as web-based tools.

SPECIALIZED SKILLS

- * Office Manager/Administrative/Coordination
- * Human Resources/Recruiting
- * Customer Service/Support
- * Computer Skills (MS Office, Google, Adobe, P2 Project SharePoint 2010, Oracle Applications 13B, CR12) QuickBooks
- * Processing Purchase Orders/Invoicing
- * Multi-Tasking and Organizational Skills
- * Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- * Travel Arrangements/Planning off/on site events

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DYCOM INDUSTRIES INC/CABLECOM, LLC

Snohomish, WA

April 2020 - Current

P2 Project Coordinator - Manage over 100 cable construction projects in the Snohomish County. Track and manage projects and milestones providing status updates while adhering to schedules. Create job estimates, prepare Bill of Materials (BOMs) to fund projects through project software (P2). Work with construction team to schedule construction jobs. Meet with General Contractors, Project Managers, or municipalities at Pre-construction open trench meetings. Process Crew Daily production for accuracy of billing and progressive as-builts with in-house and subcontractors. Pull and review reports from (P2) of project status and update job tracker. Update Supervisor for weekly meeting with Business Partner of project status regarding ECCD, SLAs and task due dates. Process invoices for approved funding. Respond to client inquiries and assist with escalations.

WAVE BROADBAND

Bothell, WA

May 2018- July 2019

Purchasing Coordinator Create, track, receive, close, change orders for purchase requests to the Washington, Oregon, and California markets within Wave Broadband. Process vendor applications to ensure terms and credit are within the company guidelines. Negotiated pricing with vendors to and delivery of materials. Main area of responsibility was managing the inventory material for the warehouses. Research and analyze material need of warehouses and changes in material to meet business needs. Backup support for purchasing team.

SHORELINE ELECTRIC

Lynnwood, WA

October 2016 - August 2017

Scheduler Answer phones and obtain an understanding of the customers need of service; schedule work to be completed by projects; track estimates in QuickBooks, worksheets, and checklists; ensure insurance certificates and bonds are up to date; research resale certificates.

COMCAST CABLE

Lynnwood, WA October 1999 – April 2016

Analyst 1/Administrative Assistant Engineering Operations

May 2007 – April 2016

Processed Network Engineering/Operations purchase orders \$25M yearly plus for the Seattle market. Maintain, prepare, and release purchase orders. Analyze, resolve, and correct issues regarding invoices with vendors to ensure accuracy and meet quarter spend targets. Ensure new vendors are entered into the system to process credit applications and setup within company guidelines. Run daily ad hock reports and post on Engineering SharePoint. Pull daily inventory part list for engineering team. Administrative Assistant to the Network Engineering team with managing calendars, coordinating travel, prepare, reconcile, and track expense reports. Experienced coordinating corporate meetings, training conferences from start to finish on and off-site locations from 2-100 participants. Purchased supplies for departments and supported projects as requested.

Recruiting Coordinator

March 2002 - May 2007

Posted job descriptions, screened resumes, tracked applicants, processed background checks, pre-employment, and post-accident drug tests. Identified local job fair recruiting activities.

Human Resources Administrative Assistant III

May 2000 - March 2002

Performed administrative support to the human resources managers to include sensitive and confidential information. Managed calendars and emails, travel arrangements, prepare correspondence, PowerPoint presentations, processing severance packages, prepare new hire orientation packages. Maintained filing systems, data bases and shared network spaces. Backup support to other departments.

Legal/Governmental Affairs Administrative Assistant II

October 1999 - May 2000

Supported the Legal and Governmental Affairs Team with administrative duties such as typing correspondence, preparing PowerPoint presentations, making travel arrangements, and managing calendars.

EDUCATION

Griffin Business College

COMMUNITY

Reading with Rover volunteer as a certified therapy team. Volunteered with my labradoodle visiting schools, libraries, assisted living facilities, colleges. **Comcast Cares** Day Lead Coordinator for three years, research non-profit organizations, select a project per company guidelines. Obtain donated material from local retailers to minimize cost of the project, operate on a limited budget, recruited approximately 100 volunteers for each project. **Big Brothers/Big Sisters**, Beyond School Walls, 3 years with the program.